CS3388 quiz1:

- afifne combinations, at least one question 
- affine space
- vector length
- matrices
- rasterization (frame buffer) including triangle rasterizations and its algoritm
- Bresenham’s algorithm (the short answer questions will most likely be on one of the line drawing algorithms)
- 2d transformations and preservations after transformations (know the notable 2d transformation matrixes)
- tell wether its affine or not based on what’s preserved
- combined transformations
- translations
- homogeneous coordinates
- finding the matrix for the transformation (similar to problem set2)
- line clipping, assumtions and when it works and doesn’t
- liang and barsky’s clipping algorithm (just know the basic stuff prolly not on it)
- Polygon clipping
- Raster Scan Polygon filling
- Anti-aliasing, how to do it in simple cases, compare the different kinds, what is meant by super-sampling (4x,8x,16x etc.)
- lerps and tweens
- basic non linear Bézier curve, won’t see a 4th degree or higher
- eulers rotation
- the camera, all of it ; not camera transformation matrix stuff
- Perspective projections
- difference between perspective and orthographic
- sudo depth
- (Euler) gimbal lock
- render pipeline
- GLSL
- 
